(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
秘密結社holoX Live 2026 「First MISSION」
[Title: Secret Society holoX Live 2026 "First MISSION"]
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
[Attention: To All Attendees]
秘密結社holoX Live 2026 「First MISSION」
#SSholoX世界リペイント計画
[Title: Secret Society holoX Live 2026 "First MISSION"]
[Hashtag: #SSholoXWorldRepaintPlan]
First MISSION 開催おめでとうございます！
応援しています！
[Message: Congratulations on holding "First MISSION"!
We're supporting you!]
holoX 初ライブおめでとう！！
ずっと大好きです！
[Message: Congratulations on holoX's first live!!
We will always love you!]
1stライブ開催本当におめでとう！
最高のステージを期待しています！
[Message: Huge congrats on holding your 1st live!
Expecting the best stage ever!]
世界中を驚かせる最高のライブに！！
頑張れholoX！！
[Message: Make it the best concert that surprises the whole world!
Good luck, holoX!!]
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
[Promotion: hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment]
ご来場のお客様へ
[Notice: Attention to Visitors]
どアニメ宣言！ JOYSOUND
[Title: Do Anime Declaration! JOYSOUND]
アニメにハマって
Hooked on anime,
歌いたくなっちゃった
I wanted to sing.
推しのシーン見ながら
Watching my favorite scene,
カラオケ歌えるなんて...
being able to sing karaoke...
尊すぎてつらいっ！
It's too precious, it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲームソング見つけよう
Let's find the anime and game songs we want to sing.
どアニメ宣言！
Do Anime Declaration!
JOYSOUND
holoplus Jack
[Promotion: holoplus Jack]
秘密結社holoX Live 2026「First MISSION」
[Visual: Secret Society holoX Live 2026 'First MISSION']
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
[Attention to the visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK.]
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
[Attention to the visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK.]
本日は、秘密結社holoX...
Today, Secret Society holoX...
秘密結社holoX Live 2026 「First MISSION」に
To Secret Society holoX Live 2026 "First MISSION,"
ご来場いただきありがとうございます！
thank you for coming today!
自己紹介！
Self-introductions!
跪け！
Kneel!
吾輩の名前はラプラス・ダークネスだ！
My name is La+ Darknesss!
みなさん、待ったー？
Did everyone wait for me?
holoXの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイと申します。
I am holoX's executive officer, Takane Lui.
みんな、こんこよー！
Everyone, Kon-Koyo!
holoXの頭脳、博衣こよりだよー！
I'm holoX's brains, Hakui Koyori!
ござるさんわー！
Gozaru-san-wa!
おー、よくできたわ。
Oh, well done.
holoXの用心棒、風真いろはでござる。
I'm holoX's bodyguard, Kazama Iroha.
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure everyone enjoys the show until the end, I have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機器の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, audio recording, and the use of filming equipment are strictly prohibited.
万が一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you feel unwell, please don't push yourself and notify a nearby staff member.
いい子です。
Good children.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
Mosh pits, diving, jumping excessively, throwing objects onto the stage...
他のみんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
...or any behavior that disturbs others or disrupts the show is forbidden.
また、3階と4階の最前列席は危険防止のため立ち見禁止です。
Additionally, standing is prohibited in the front row seats on the 3rd and 4th floors.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね。
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
お守りいただけない場合、ご退場いただく可能性がございます。
Failure to comply may result in your removal from the venue.
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
Also, cameras for live streaming and photography are present in the venue,
客席が映り込む場合がございます。
and the audience may be captured on film.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
These videos and photos may be used for promotion. Thank you for your understanding.
いい返事だな。
That's a good response.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは #SSholoX世界リペイント計画 です。
Also, the hashtag for the show is #SSholoXWorldRepaintPlan.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください！
Please use the hashtag to share the excitement!
それでは、開演までもう少しです。
Well then, the show will start shortly.
みんなで一緒に盛り上がるでござる！
Let's all get fired up together!
みんな、しーっ。静かに、静かに。
Everyone, shh. Quietly now, quietly.
「そこに跪け！」
"Kneel before us!"
「吐いて捨てるような現実を」
"We are slashing through the disposable reality"
「一刀両断叩き斬る」
"Slicing it in one strike!"
「終わりなき輪廻に迷いし子らよ」
"Children lost in the endless samsara"
「漆黒의 翼で誘おう」
"Let us lure you with our jet-black wings"
「我らエデンの星を統べる者、 秘密結社…」
"We are the rulers of the stars of Eden, Secret Society..."
「holoX!!」
"holoX!!"
ウォッオー ウォッオッオッ オーオーオー
Woah-oh Woah-oh-oh Oh-oh-oh
How Low? どうしようもないこの世界
How Low? This world is hopeless
(どうして欲しい？)
(What do you want?)
Black Out 終末告げる鐘が鳴る
Black Out The bell signaling the end is ringing
ラッパッパッパラ パって踊ろうぜ Tripしようぜ
Ra-pa-pa-pa-ra Let's dance together, Let's take a trip
陰キャも陽キャも Sing a Song
Introverts and extroverts too, Sing a Song
気持ちいいことだけが すべて 堕ちて いく 闇の底へ
Everything is just about feeling good, Falling down into the bottom of the darkness
甘い甘い メロディ ほら どうぞ どうぞ 手の鳴る方へ
Sweet, sweet melody, here you go, here you go, towards where the hands are clapping
もう逃げられない ほら 闇に染まれば 世界を塗り替えろ
Already can't escape, look, once you're stained in darkness, Repaint the world
望めばくれてやろう すべて
If you wish for it, we'll give it to you, everything
常識 破り捨てろ くるくる狂い倒せ 火を付けろ
Break the common sense, spin around and go crazy, light the fire
(ラッパッパーラッパッ)
(Ra-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa)
すべてを喰らいつくせ
Devour everything
(ラッパッパーラッパッ)
(Ra-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa)
秘密を 教えてやろう
We will teach you the secret
ウォッオー ウォーッオーオー オーオーオー
Woah-oh Woah-oh-oh Oh-oh-oh
悪のカリスマ 導くぞ民草
Charisma of evil, leading the commoners
正義とか知らないし 地鳴らして誘い
We don't know about justice, Luring them while shaking the ground
マジメに不真面目 弊社の通過儀礼
Earnestly not serious, the passing ritual of our company
望み求め 願い叶え 世界征服
Seek your wishes, grant your desires, world conquest
ラーパッパって歌おうぜ Swingしようぜ
Let's sing Ra-pa-pa, let's Swing together
退屈な世界へ Bye Bye Bye
Bye Bye Bye to the boring world
覚めることのない夢を 魅せる ほら お眠りなさい
We will show you a dream that never ends, Here, go to sleep
もっともっと 奥へ ほら どうぞ どうぞ イキたいんでしょ？
More, more, deeper, Here, go ahead, go ahead, you want to go, right?
もうやめられない ほら 悪に染まれば 世界を塗り替えろ
Already can't stop, look, once you're stained in evil, Repaint the world
望むもの与えよう すべて
We'll give you what you want, everything
ルールを書き換えろ くるくる回し尽くせ 焼き尽くす
Rewrite the rules, spin it all around, Burn it down
(ラッパッパーラッパッ)
(Ra-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa)
すべてのマガイモノへ
Towards all the imposters
(ラッパッパーラッパッ)
(Ra-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa)
秘密を 教えてやろう
We will teach you the secret
「機は熟した！狂気の宴の始まりだ！ 貴様ら、準備はいいか！！」
"The time is ripe! The banquet of madness begins! You guys, are you ready!!"
「お～～！！！」
"Ohhh!!!"
「刮目せよ！！」
"Behold!!"
(クロヱ！！クロヱ！！)
(Chloe!! Chloe!!)
「手あげろ！手あげろ！！」
"Hands up! Hands up!!"
(いろは！！いろは！！)
(Iroha!! Iroha!!)
「叫ぶでござる～！」
"Scream!!"
(こより！！こより！！)
(Koyori!! Koyori!!)
「踊っちゃえ！踊っちゃえ！！」
"Dance! Dance!!"
「世界を手にするholoX！ 世界を変えていくholoX！」
"holoX taking the world! holoX changing the world!"
(ルイ姉！ルイ姉！！)
(Lui-nee! Lui-nee!!)
「もっともっと！！」
"More, more!!"
(ラプラス！ラプラス！！)
(Laplus! Laplus!!)
「最後は全員いくぞ！」
"Last one, everyone let's go!"
(holoX！holoX！！)
(holoX! holoX!!)
「世界を手にするholoX！」
"holoX taking the world!"
「世界を変えてくholoX！ 世界をこの手にholoX！」
"holoX changing the world! holoX with the world in its hands!"
心を 解き放て ほら どうぞ どうぞ 身を任せて
Set your heart free, here you go, here you go, surrender yourself
もう逃げられない ほら 闇に染まれば 世界を塗り替えろ
Already can't escape, look, once you're stained in darkness, Repaint the world
望めばくれてやろう すべて
If you wish for it, we'll give it to you, everything
常識 破り捨てろ くるくる狂い倒せ 火を付けろ
Break the common sense, spin around and go crazy, light the fire
(ラッパッパーラッパッ)
(Ra-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa)
すべてを喰らいつくせ
Devour everything
(ラッパッパーラッパッ)
(Ra-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa)
秘密を 教えてやろう
We will teach you the secret
ウォッオー ウォーオーオー オーオーオー
Woah-oh Woah-oh-oh Oh-oh-oh
hololive production presents.
2026 First MISSION
holoX Live 2026 "First MISSION"
【総帥】 ラプラス・ダークネス
[Leader] La+ Darknesss
【幹部】 鷹嶺ルイ
[Executive] Takane Lui
【研究者】 博衣こより
[Researcher] Hakui Koyori
【用心棒】 風真いろは
[Bodyguard] Kazama Iroha
Are You Ready?
我ら、エデンの星を統べる者！
We, who rule the stars of Eden!
秘密結社holoX、見参！
Secret Society holoX, arrival!
好機は熟した！
The time is ripe!
深淵より現れし眷属たちよ！
You followers who have appeared from the abyss!
準備はいいか！
Are you ready?!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
Are you ready?
夜が深まる ほら darkness
The night deepens, look, darkness
脳を溶かして ポッケに隠す
Melt your brain and hide it in your pocket
何したええの？ エゴイスティックに
What should I do? Egoistically
もっと密に サムライガール
More closely, samurai girl
病みつきしないけど フルベットで
I'm not addicted, but with a full bet...
絶望的？ 地に咲く 赤字を ジャッキンジャッキン
Desperate? Scattering red ink, jackin' jackin'
悪の手の平 踊ってみなよ
Dance on the palm of evil
御陀仏に... 気づけば ノリノリです
To the pyre... before I knew it, I'm grooving
どうしようもない
It can't be helped
宇宙的
Cosmic
全部塗り替えよう
Let's repaint it all
X to the X to the X
交差する 真ん中で
At the center where they cross
Next to the Next to the Next
限界はもう始まってる
The limit has already begun
扉の向こう側が呼ぶ方へ
Towards where the other side of the door calls
愛憎交わす X です
Love and hate exchanging, it's X
混沌としたこの世界を
This chaotic world
我らholoX色に 塗り替えるのだ！
We shall repaint it in holoX colors!
皆の者、かかれ！
Everyone, attack!
Yes, My Dark!
Absolute Darkness Infinity!
エデンの星は 我が手中に
Eden's star is in my hands
風穴 開けたんだ
I've opened a wind tunnel
支配は 始まった
The rule has begun
息はもう かけたの
I've already cast my spell
罰ゾーンの 資格ないはずよ
You shouldn't have the qualification for the penalty zone
抑えきれない 自力制御不能のパワー
Unstoppable, self-uncontrollable power
捕まえてみなよ 影も形もない My heart
Try and catch it, my shadowless, shapeless heart
半信半疑な 素振りは No No
Doubtful behavior is No No
心に従って
Follow your heart
忠誠心見せてよ 今こそ
Show your loyalty now
Ready Lady Ready Go
Da Da La La Da La Dark
RA PA PAN PAN PAN
You will want it more, want it more
Ey！ You will love it now, love it
RA PA PAN PAN PAN
風穴開けたんだ 支配は始まった
I've punched a hole in this world. My reign has begun.
息はもう掛けたの But you don’t know
I've already cast my spell, but you don’t know.
自覚ないはずよ (huff-n-puff)
You're probably not even aware of it (huff-n-puff).
抑え切れない自力制御不能なPower (Power)
Unstoppable, uncontrollable Power (Power).
捕まえてみなよ 影形もない My heart
Try and catch it, my heart with no shadow or form.
(I’m so crazy crazy in love)
半信半疑な素振りはNo no
No half-hearted gestures, no no.
心に従って 忠誠心見せてよ
Follow your heart and show me your loyalty.
お待たせ。秘密結社holoXの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイだ。
Thanks for waiting. I am Takane Lui, the female executive of holoX.
お前もホロクサーの一員となるのだ！
You too shall become a member of the Holoxers!
単純で明快で簡単じゃないまだ
It's simple and clear, but not easy yet.
想像と妄想と偏見でWhy
With imagination, delusion, and prejudice, why?
そりゃ完全な万全な設定じゃないから
Well, the setting isn't completely perfect,
かってくれないか
so won't you tease me?
外見と内面と偶像の不一致
The mismatch between appearance, inner self, and idol.
この繊細さ敏感さ共有しよ
Let's share this delicacy and sensitivity.
ほら冷静な表情は実際ちょーハイ
See, this calm expression is actually super high.
見つけてくれないか
Won't you find me?
はいはいお姉さんしまっちゃって行こう
Yes, yes, big sister, let's pack it up and go.
はいはい期待感背負っちゃって行こう
Yes, yes, let's carry those expectations and go.
はいはいお姉さんしまっちゃって行こう
Yes, yes, big sister, let's pack it up and go.
はいはい期待感背負っちゃって行こう
Yes, yes, let's carry those expectations and go.
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど
Holo-holo hawk, holo-hawk, but...
高嶺の花みたいに扱っちゃ嫌
Don't treat me like an unattainable flower.
あのね誰も彼も鷲と勘違い
You know, everyone mistakes me for an eagle.
驚きの目(アイ)
What surprising eyes (I).
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど
Holo-holo hawk, holo-hawk, but...
PONコツみがちょいあるだけで親近感
Just being a bit of a klutz makes me feel closer.
その際その差異その才受け止めてよね
Accept that timing, that difference, and that talent.
鷹嶺の未来乾杯
A toast to the future of Takane.
ノーイーグル しっかりウォッチ
No eagle, watch closely.
ノーイーグル 曖昧You Know
No eagle, vague You Know.
ノーイーグル 狩りとか苦手
No eagle, not good at hunting.
ノーイーグル 猛禽ルイ姉
No eagle, raptor Lui-sister.
ノーイーグル 一見クールね
No eagle, looks cool at first glance.
ノーイーグル 意外とギャップ系
No eagle, surprisingly a gap-type.
ノーイーグル イメージ大変身
No eagle, huge image makeover.
ノーイーグル OK？
No eagle, OK?
大衆の歓声って内蔵じゃない？
Isn't the roar of the crowd like an organ?
ありゃ心配ね相談ね散々ね
That's worrying, a consultation, just terrible.
もうただ正論や暴論の配信じゃない！
This isn't just a stream of logic and rants!
個人的見解対正解
Personal opinion versus the correct answer.
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど
Holo-holo hawk, holo-hawk, but...
捕食しないさだから怖がっちゃ嫌
I don't prey on things, so don't be afraid.
ほらね爪も羽もお洒落に研いで
See, I sharpen my claws and feathers stylishly,
隠しちゃいない
and I'm not hiding them.
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど
Holo-holo hawk, holo-hawk, but...
観察目がちょいあるだけで緊張感
Just having observant eyes creates tension.
こよりんのパワー！
Koyorin's power!
これで君もこよりんにメロメロだー！
With this, you'll be head over heels for Koyorin too!
えへ、えへへ、えへへ…
Ehe, ehehe, ehehe...
みんなの脳みそに、お注射しちゃうぞ～～～～！！
I'm going to give everyone's brains an injection!
実験だ！実験だ！実験！実験！実験だ！ 実験だ！実験だ！(うぉ～～～わっふー！)
Experiment! Experiment! Experiment! Experiment! (Uooh waffu!)
実験だ！実験だ！実験！実験！実験だ！ 実験だ！実験だ！実・験・だ～～～！
Experiment! Experiment! Ex-per-i-ment!
研究 研究 研究 耐久回 急上昇中
Research, Research, Research! Endurance streams rising!
呼ばれて飛び出て バビブベボ BOOM！(BOOM！)
Called out and popped out, Ba-bi-bu-be-bo BOOM! (BOOM!)
検証 検証 検証 CAUTION アテンションプリーズ(プリーズ！)
Verification! Verification! Verification! CAUTION, Attention please!
舐めてたら火傷しちゃうョ
If you take me lightly, you'll get burned.
(マヨ！)迷ったらダメダメ (マヨ！)真夜中サイエンス
(Mayo!) Don't get lost, no no! (Mayo!) Midnight science.
(マヨ！)魔除けの呪文は マヨマヨちゅっちゅ！(ちゅっちゅ！)
(Mayo!) The warding spell is Mayo-Mayo kiss! (Kiss!)
(こよ！)今宵のデザート (こよ！)高揚するHeart Beat
(Koyo!) Tonight's dessert! (Koyo!) High Heart Beat!
(こよ！)こよりこよられ 恋焦がれ～ (わっふー！)
(Koyo!) Longing for Koyori (Waffu!)
サイン → コサイン → タンジェント(Ay)
Sine -> Cosine -> Tangent (Ay)
試験管 → Docking → ダイレクト(Ay)
Test tube -> Docking -> Direct (Ay)
白衣の天使が降臨！(^_^)ノヤッホー！！
The angel in a white coat has descended! Yoo-hoo!!
天才天才天才 とんでもなく偉い
Genius, genius, genius! Ridiculously great!
崇めちゃってOK 褒めてくスタイル
It's okay to worship me, that's my style!
最高最高最高 そんでラブって優勝
Best, best, best! And love for the win!
ぶっちゃけ 脳内シュワシュワ スタンディングオベーション
Honestly, my brain is fizzing. Standing ovation!
(Wow-o-o-o) 科学とは
(Wow-o-o-o) Science is...
(Wow-o-o-o) 爆発だ
(Wow-o-o-o) an explosion!
ポチッとピポパ 間違えてドッカーン
Click-click pipopa, mistake-bang!
ドジなトコも 計算通りよ
Even the clumsy parts are all as calculated.
実験だ！実験だ！実験！実験！実験だ！ 実験だ！実験だ！(うぉ～～～わっふー！)
Experiment! Experiment! Experiment! Experiment! (Uooh waffu!)
実験だ！実験だ！実験！実験！実験だ！ 実験だ！実験だ！実・験・だ～～～！
Experiment! Experiment! Ex-per-i-ment!
さぁ～て、もっと声出せるよね！
Now then, you can yell louder than that, right?!
じゃあ一緒に、実験だーって叫ぶよ！
Then together, we're going to shout 'Experiment'!
せーの！ 実験だーー！！
Ready, go! Experiment!!
（実験だ！実験だ！実験だ！実験だ！）
(Experiment! Experiment! Experiment!)
ありがとう！
Thank you!
疾風、此処にあり！
The Gale is here!
行きます！
Here I go!
一刀両断叩き斬る!
I'll slice you in two!
心の寄せる ほのかな唄
A faint song that draws the heart closer
花の芽になりたい 一つ突く その前より
I want to be a flower bud. Even before the first strike...
しっかりと 地に立ちたい 唇を 芽吹かせる
I want to stand firmly on the ground and let my lips bloom.
やらずの雨が降ろうと 出し抜けに 啜ることなく
Even if it rains to stop me, without even a sip unexpectedly...
八百万の声を灯せば 由縁もありし日の 記録にできるから
If I light up the myriad voices, I can turn fated days into a record.
涙など もう いじるのが 苦手... 咲く
I'm no longer good at playing with tears... I'll bloom.
福桜を 散りまければ 愛されない 後ろめたさ も
If the lucky cherry blossoms scatter, even the guilt of being unloved...
叫を 勝ち割るぐらい 身を切るぐらいに 凪を打つ 有明の 先で
To the point of splitting the cry or cutting my body, I'll strike the calm at dawn.
心の寄せる ほのかな唄
A faint song that draws the heart closer
どうしようもない Don't show, No mine
It can't be helped, Don't show, No mine
堕ちてく運命 ならしょうがない
If it's our destiny to fall, then it can't be helped
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's repaint everything now
刮目せよ!!
Witness this!!
XとXとXとXが交差する真ん中で
In the center where X, X, X, and X intersect
Next Next Next 世界はもう始まってる じゃん!!!!
Next Next Next, the world has already begun, right!!!!
媚びな complete now つまり最後に
Don't flatter, complete now, so in the end...
笑うのはholoXです
The ones laughing will be holoX
holoXのライブが始まったぞー!
The holoX live concert has begun!
おにぎりー! こんにちはー!
Onigiri! Hello everyone!
全然秘匿性のない秘密結社...
A secret society with absolutely no secrecy...
自己紹介する? はい!
Shall we introduce ourselves? Yes!
じゃあ、狂気の宴の始まりだー!
Now then, let the banquet of madness begin!
貴様ら、刮目せよ!
You all, witness this!
吾輩の名前は、ラプラス・ダークネスだ!
My name is La+ Darknesss!
はい! 皆様、待ったー?
Yes! Everyone, did you wait for me?
新しいのよ。やってくれた、みんな。
This is new. You guys were great.
holoXの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイと申します!
I am the female executive of holoX, Takane Lui!
待った? 待った?
Did you wait? Did you wait?
はい! ちょっと新しいの行きますね
Yes! I'm going to try something a bit new.
あの子より、その子より...
More than that girl, more than that girl...
こよりー!
It's Koyori!
いけてるじゃん、すごーい! ありがとう
That was cool, amazing! Thank you.
holoXの頭脳、博衣こよりだよー!
I'm the brain of holoX, Hakui Koyori!
お前たち、わかってるよね? わかってるよね?
You guys understand, right? You understand, right?
ござるさんはー? かわいいー!
Gozaru-san is...? She's cute!
holoX好き? もう一回! ござるさんはー?
Do you like holoX? One more time! Gozaru-san is...?
かわいいー!
She's cute!
強いぞ！かっこいいぞ！
Strong! Cool!
用心棒侍の
The bodyguard samurai,
風真いろはでござるー！
Kazama Iroha de gozaru!
うーわ、ついにこの日が
Whoa, this day has finally...
きてしまった！
...arrived!
始まっちゃった！
It's started!
見捨てられなかった！
I wasn't abandoned!
危ない危ない！
That was close, that was close!
最初のメドレー
That opening medley...
すごかったでしょ？
...was amazing, right?
みんなこんな風に
Did everyone...
混ざって踊って歌って
...expect us to mix it up,
予想できてたー？
dancing and singing like that?
できないよね！
I bet you didn't!
絶対無理！
No way at all!
だよねだよね！
Right, right!
予想通りだわ。
Just as I thought.
もう最初から
It's been a climax...
クライマックス並みの盛り上がりで
...from the very start.
それぐらいの盛り上がりで本当。
Seriously, the excitement was on that level.
始まったばっかだけどね。
Even though we just started.
始まったばっかと言えばさ、
Speaking of just starting...
もうみんな、あの自己紹介の時に、
...everyone was already getting a bit teary...
実はみんなもうちょっとうるっときてて。
...during the introductions earlier.
やめろその話は！
Stop talking about that!
いや、なんならもう、
I mean, even before that,
楽屋の時点で、
back in the dressing room,
ルイさんは...
Lui-san was...
一番早かったのはルイさん！
Lui-san was the first one!
いつもルイから！
It's always starting with Lui!
違うのよルイさん、違うのよ。
That's not it, Lui-san, that's not it.
違うのよ。
It's not that.
花粉症！
Hay fever!
誤魔化すなよ！
Don't try to hide it!
ごまかさないで！
Don't cover it up!
花粉症！
Hay fever!
いいじゃん、素直に！
It's fine, just be honest!
メンバー大好きーとか言って泣き出して。
Saying 'I love the members' and starting to cry.
吾輩も好きー！
I love them too!
やめてよ！恥ずかしい！
Stop it! It's embarrassing!
それをさ、みんなずっと弄ってたのに、
Everyone was teasing her about it,
ここに来てみんなの笑顔を見たらさ...
but once we got out here and saw everyone's smiles...
うっ、うるっときちゃう。
...we all got a bit choked up.
始まる前はみんなこんな感じで待ってたのに、
Before it started, everyone was waiting like this,
自己紹介始まった瞬間、
but the moment the introductions began...
うるうるうるーって！
...we were all tearing up!
めっちゃ笑顔で「んー！」みたいになって、
We had big smiles, but we were like 'Mmm!'
みんなの声とか音とか凄くて、
Everyone's voices and the sound were so intense,
みんな泣いてた。
we were all crying.
そう、うるっときちゃった。でも、
Yeah, we got teary. But,
やらなきゃって！
we knew we had to do this!
やったんだよね、うん。
And we did it, yeah.
やらないといけないよね！
We have to give it our all!
今日はかまさないといけないよね！
We've got to blow everyone away today!
でも1曲目はかませたんじゃないか？
But I think we definitely nailed that first song!
かませてたー！
We totally did!
最初の曲のメドレーのさ、
That opening medley,
タイトル言ってやってよ！
go ahead and say the title!
ちょっと待って、これ読むの？
Wait a sec, am I supposed to read this?
めっちゃカッコよく言えるよ！
I can say it really cool!
代表して！お願いします！
Representing us! Please!
みんな「今日X」はみんな知ってるよねー！
Everyone knows 'KyouX', right?
今日の目的のために特別タイトルあるから！
There's a special title for today's mission!
そうなのよ。
That's right.
いくぜ！
Here we go!
今日Xです！エクステンドリミックス！
It's KyouX! Extend Remix!
みんなの必殺技詰め込んでみましたバージョン！
The 'Packed with Everyone's Special Moves' Version!
なんか最後、そのままじゃない？
Isn't the last part just exactly what it says?
無理やりじゃない？
Isn't that a bit forced?
カッコイイ！
It's cool!
カッコよかったぜ！決まったぜ！
That was cool! You nailed it!
配信組も盛り上がってますかー？
Is the streaming crew getting hyped too?
配信カメラがあるよ！あ、配信カメラがあるよ！
The streaming camera is over there! Oh, there it is!
いえーい！お前らー！
Yeah! You guys!
コメントも見えてるからね！
We can see your comments too!
コメントも「いえーい！」「うおー！」しか言ってない！
The comments are just 'Yeah!' and 'Whoa!'
「タイトル長い」って言わないで！
Don't say 'The title is too long'!
長くないぞ！
It's not too long!
吾輩の名前より短いじゃん！
It's shorter than my name!
まあそう、そうね。
Well, that's true.
もうみんな開演前から気づいたと思うけど、
I think everyone noticed before the show started,
DJー！
the DJ!
最高だぜ！落ちないようにね！
You're the best! Don't fall off!
本当だよ、ちょっと怖いよ。
Seriously, it's a bit scary.
あそこ超高いぜ！
It's super high up there!
というわけで、
And so,
ここから先は、本当の任務に入っていくぞ！
from here on, we're heading into the real mission!
行くぞー！始まったんだ！
Let's go! It's finally starting!
なんですけど、ここで...
But, at this point...
嫌だ！俺は聞かないぞ！
No! I'm not listening!
悲しい...
So sad...
まさか、流石に...
No way, surely...
ちょっと私から言うのはアレなんで、こよりさん！
It's hard for me to say, so Koyori-san!
おいおいおい！その口を借りるな！
Hey, hey, hey! Don't use her voice for that!
はい、ではちょっと大事なお知らせです。
Okay, we have an important announcement.
YouTube、TikTokライブでご覧になっている方、
For those watching on YouTube and TikTok Live,
無料チラ見せは...
this free preview...
ここまでとなります！
...ends here!
会場内に関係ないのに「えー」って言ってくれてる。
Even people here in the venue are going 'Ehh~'.
みんな見れるのにね。優しい優しい。
Even though you can see it all. So kind.
ですが！この後も...
However! After this...
あんなパフォーマンスや、ゴージャスな楽曲など、
...performances like that and gorgeous songs,
今からでも間に合いますので、この辺！
...there's still time to catch them! Around here!
概要欄から、この辺！配信チケットを購入してください！
From the description, right here! Please buy a stream ticket!
ここ！ここここここ！ここです！
Here! Right here! Over here!
役回りの上！
Stay in character!
お前ら！絶対買えよな！
You guys! You'd better buy them!
買った音した、買った音。あれヤバイよ。
I heard the sound of purchases. That was crazy.
そしてこのライブの感想などはですね、
And for your thoughts on this live show,
ハッシュタグ「SSホロックス世界リペイント計画」でポストしてくださいね！
please post using the hashtag #SSholoXWorldRepaintProject!
お願いします！
Please do!
そしてそして！配信組はいっぱいスクショ撮ってアップしてね！
And! Streaming crew, take lots of screenshots and upload them!
お願いします！盛り上げて！シャカシャカ！
Please! Get hyped! Snap-snap!
ってことで
So then...
じゃあここからね、さっき言ってた通り
Well then, from here, just as we were saying earlier...
本当のミッション始まりますなね！
The true mission is starting, isn't it!
はい！
Yes!
おーい！まだ声出せるよなー！
Hey! You can still make some noise, right?!
おー、いいよ！
Ooh, nice!
最高です！
You're the best!
ここにいる全員、そして配信民！
Everyone here, and those watching the stream!
覚悟はいいかー！
Are you ready?!
ファーストミッション、ここからが本番だ！
First Mission, the real show starts now!
それでは、任務続行！
And now, mission continue!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[The free part has ended!
Thank you for watching!]
無料パートは終了いたしました！ ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.]